Ideation test upload
--
Pizza Delivery Game
I’ve got one idea for a game that could be interesting: it’s kind of like the original Grand theft auto except just a pizza delivery person have two things they must do: a platform game when I arrive at the location to deliver the pizza :pizza: and a top-down car game when they’re driving to the location and maybe some mini games or something in the actual pizza shop and then they arrive to deliver the pizza.
If we could we could get some networking, going and have people delivering pizzas at the same time and with the car game that means they can interact with each other or possibly compete with each other when they’re actually doing the platform part of the game.
---
